Guide to the Media Services records, [ca. 1950-2015.]
Media Services records, [ca. 1950-2015]
- Series III: Slides
  - "Coastal Erosion and Real Property Values" Original Slides - Cornell Film, 1985 (Box 21-36-2566 - 16)
  - "Hatch Act Centennial 1887-1987 Slide Show" 140 Slides - Cornell Film, 1987 (Box 21-36-2566 - 16)
  - "The Business of Food Shopping" 80 Slides (Box 21-36-2566 - 16)
  - "Growing and Use of Common Herbs" - Descriptions of 31 herbs, with hints, uses, and folklore. 38 Slides - Cornell Film (Box 21-36-2566 - 16)
  - "Come In and Play" - Portable, inexpensive play environment for children ages 2-3. 77 Slides - Cornell Film, 1981 (Box 21-36-2566 - 16)
  - "Understanding Predation" -- Human attitudes towards predators, and the role of predators in natural systems. 62 Slides - Cornell Film, 1980 (Box 21-36-2566 - 16)
  - "Understanding Northeastern Birds of Prey" - Close-up photos of northeastern raptors. Diversity, roles in the ecosystem, and conservation. 77 Slides - Cornell Film, 1980 (Box 21-36-2566 - 16)
  - "Understanding Oil/Gas Heating Systems" - Cornell Film (Box 21-36-2566 - 16)
  - "Babies in Family Day Care" - Development and enhancement of successful out-of-home child care arrangements. 93 Slides - Cornell Film, 1979 (Box 21-36-2566 - 16)
  - "But What Do You Do With Them?" - Day care environments for babies from 3 to 11 months at the Cornell Infant Nursery. 130 Slides - Cornell Film, 1972 (Box 21-36-2566 - 16)
  - "Be a Pro: Avoid Pesticide Accidents" - Illustration of safe storage, handling, and cleanup of pesticides. Designed for use in certification training of pesticide applicators. 79 Slides - Cornell Film, 1974 (Box 21-36-2566 - 16)
  - "Be a Pro with Pesticides"-- Alternatives to handling and application techniques shown in the film by the same name. 72 Slides - Cornell Film, 1974 (Box 21-36-2566 - 16)
  - "Come Out and Play" - Slides and workbook designed to assist parents or community in designing and building a playground. 63 Slides - Cornell Film, 1974 (Box 21-36-2566 - 16)
  - "Selection and Planting" - How to select and plant trees for specific areas. 41 Slides. - Cornell Film, 1981 (Box 21-36-2566 - 16)
  - "Always Wear the Right Stuff!" Audio Tape and Script in English and Spanish - Charlotte Coffman - Cornell Film, 1994 (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - "Closed Systems for Handling Liquid Pesticides" - Cornell Film, 1985 (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - "Coastal Erosion and Real Property Values" - Cornell Film, 1984 (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - "Cobbler's Cove: Coastal Planning Simulation Game" - Sandor Schuman - Cornell Film, 1980 (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - "Culture of Garden Roses" - no script - Cornell Film, 1963 (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - "Energy: Our Food and Our Needs" - Susan Travis and Barbara Fry - Cornell Film, 1984 (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - "Extension Home Economics: A Force for Families" - no script - Cornell Film (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - "Foundation for the Future" - Cornell Film, 1982 (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - "Expanding the World of Cooperative Extension" - no script - Cornell Film, 1972 (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - "Iron: The Blood Building Nutrient" - Developed for EFNEP - Deborah Edwards (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - "Iron: The Hard-to-Get Nutrient" - Developed for EFNEP - Deborah Edwards and Patty Redihan - Cornell Film, 1986 (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - "Keeping Cool in Actionwear" - no script - Cornell Film, 1986 (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - "Learning with Love" - Family day care - Cornell Film, 1975 (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - "Oil Analysis: Maintenance Technique" - Gene Feldman - Cornell Film, 1982 (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - "Oil and Gas Production on Your New York State Land" - Cornell Film, 1987 (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - "Pressure Canning Know-How" - Klippstein - slide/tape program, 1977 (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - "Radon Gas in the Home Environment" - Joseph LaQuatra - Cornell Film (also on video), 1988 (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - "Selecting Sports Equipment: Football" - no script or tape - Cornell Film (also on video), 1988 (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - "Strategy for Healthy Bedding Plant Production" - Margery Daughtery and Ralph Freeman - Cornell Film, 1983 (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - "Take Control of Your Finances" - Jeanne Hogarth - Cornell Film (also on video), 1984 (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - "Places and Spaces:Silent Partners in School-Age Child Care" - Jennifer Birckmayer - slide/tape program, 1991 (Box 21-36-2566 - 17)
  - Historical slides of campus scenes, faculty and buildings, Various dates (Box 21-36-2566 - 34)
- Series IV. Videotapes
  - A. Childcare and Family Issues
    - "School Age Child Care", V-6885 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "What is Family Daycare?", V-6886 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Day Care Council - Every Community Needs One", V-6887 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Developmentally Appropriate Activities for School-Age Children", V-6888 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Lunch Time with Babies 2", V-6889 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Nutrition Puppets", V-6890 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Creating a Positive Space for School Age Child Care" Part 1, V-6891 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Creating a Positive Space for School Age Child Care" Part 2, V-6892 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Caring for School-Age Children: Effective Partnerships", June 7, 1997; V-6893 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Caring for Kids: Three Approaches" - Produced by Mary Agnes Hamilton, Directed by D.H. Gluck - Photosynthesis Productions, 1987; V-6894 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Three Worlds of Childhood", V-6895 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Children Speak Out: You Have the Right!", V-6896 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Child Abuse: A Perspective on Being a Parent" (also on film), V-6897 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Child Abuse: The Childrens' Perspective", V-6898 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Child Abuse: A Total Treatment Perspective" (also on film), V-6999 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Brianna, A Two Year-Old in a Group Setting", V-6900 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Parents, Teachers, and the Community Building Partnerships...", V-6901 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Tyner - Shared Parenting" Volume 1, V-6902 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Tyner - Shared Parenting" Volume 2, V-6903 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Talking with Teens", V-6904 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "I Still Can't Say It", V-6905 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "The American Family: Who Cares?" (Use DVD-979 in same box), 1976; V-6884 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
      Click here to see a digitized version of the video.
      A taped lecture of Professor Urie Bronfenbrenner discussing the break-up of the traditional American family, the general state of isolation and the impact on children and society.
    - Use copy of "The American Family: Who Cares?", DVD-979 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "American Family: in 1984", V-6906 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Treating the Incestuous Family", V-6907 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Family Matters" with Film Discussion Guide, 1985; V-6908 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Families in the Balance", V-6909 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Housing Options for Older People" (also on film), V-6910 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "The Choice is Yours: Housing Options for Seniors Today", V-6911 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - "Problems of the Elderly: Last Thing on My Mind" (also on film), 1973; V-6912 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
  - B. Agriculture, Horticulture, Soil Science, Chemical Safety
    - "Chemical Series - Preview Tape", V-11195 (Box 21-36-2566 - ?)
    - "Chemical Safety for General Service Workers", V-11196 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Chemical Safety for Laboratory Workers", V-11197 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "New York State Sea Grant Extension Program: The Waterfront Legacy", V-11198 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Orange County Agriculture: A Growing Industry", V-11199 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Americana Trail Experience", V-11200 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Sidewalks of Shade" (also on film and on YouTube), V-11201 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Daylight Savings: Four Season Solar Home" (also on film), V-11202 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Cornell Plantations: A Year in the Garden", V-11203 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Cornell Plantations", V-11204 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Food Science: A Proud Past and a Promising Future", V-11205 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Barn Ventilation", V-11206 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Ejaculation in the Bull", V-11207 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Incubation and Embryology: A Teaching Package" Unit 1, V-11208 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Incubation and Embryology: A Teaching Package" Unit 2, V-11209 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Observing Living Chicken Embryos", V-11210 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Poultry Killing and Dressing", V-11211 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Soil Taxonomy: A Technical Language of Soil Science", V-11212 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Keys to Soil Taxonomy", V-11213 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Land with Love and Respect" (also on film), V-11214 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Altered Landscapes", V-11215 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Land Drainage" (also on film), V-11216 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Sand Dune Erosion Project", V-11217 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Groundwater Quality, Quantity, or Crisis", V-11218 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Potential for Contamination of Groundwater by Abandoned Landfills: Airphoto" with slide script, V-11219 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Nonpoint Source Pollution: An Educational Program for the Northeast", V-11220 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Nonpoint Source Pollution Control: An Educational Program for the Northeast", V-11221 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Watershed Conflict Resolution", V-11222 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences", V-11223 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Pruning Grapes", V-11224 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Scouting for Common Alfalfa Diseases", V-11225 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "S.I.M.P. - A Guide to Apple Sampling in New York State", V-11226 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Potassium for Agriculture", V-11227 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Snap Bean Pest Management", V-11228 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
    - "Swarming in Honeybees", V-11229 (Box 21-36-2566 - 32)
  - C. Business, Finance, Safety, Miscellaneous
    - "Home Heating with Wood" (also on film), V-11230 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Stretching Mobile Home Heating Dollars", V-11231 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Radon Gas in the Home Environment", V-11232 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Switched On Kitchen", V-11233 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Be a Better Shopper" promo, V-11234 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Take Control of Your Finances", V-11235 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "You're Accountable" (English verison with booklet), V-11236 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "You're Accountable" (Spanish version), V-11237 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Concept Mapping" with booklet, V-11238 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Interview Techniques" Unit 1, V-11239 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Interview Techniques" Unit 2, V-11240 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Interview Techniques" Unit 3, V-11241 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Bar Yohai", V-11242 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
      On CornellCast
    - "The Time of Your Life", V-11243 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Be Somebody: Stay Out of Trouble with Alcohol", V-11244 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Make Up Your Mind About Alcohol", V-11245 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Life, Sciences and Society: Drugs that Alter the Mind", V-11246 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Stop Date Rape", V-11247 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Light and Easy - A Measure of Reponsiblity" Part 1, V-11248 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Light and Easy - A Measure of Responsiblity" Part 2, V-11249 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Championship Material", V-11250 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Selecting Sports Equipment: Football", V-11251 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Everyone Pays for Potholes", V-11252 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Samantha "Rastles" The Woman Question (Performance)", V-11253 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Samantha "Rastles" The Woman Question (Questions and Answers)", V-11254 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Clothing for People with Special Needs", V-11255 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Charterboat Fishing Customers", V-11256 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Communicating with Customers", V-11257 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Blue: A Tlingit Odyssey", V-11258 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - "Cycle: A Cameraless Animated Film by Robert Ascher" with booklet, V-11259 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - Planned Giving, V-11260 (Box 21-36-2566 - 33)
    - Al Seckel Lecture - "Your Mind's Eye: The World's Most Powerful Illusions", 2004-09-14; V-9374, V-9375 (Box 21-36-2566 - 31)
    - Chinese Figures: the Cornell-China-Oxford Project on Nutrition, Health and Environment, 1992-05; V-9366 (Box 35-14-3773 - 13)
    - Close Ties: You, Cornell and the Planned Giving Advantage, 1994; V-9367 (Box 35-14-3773 - 13)
    - The Power and Promise of Life Sciences - Cornell Alumni Affairs and Development, 2003; V-9757 (Box 35-14-3773 - 13)
      Spring
  - Subseries IVa. Videotapes transferred from Distributed Learning Services
    - American Airlines, March 11, 2008; V-1511; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Antigone, tr8314 - tr8316; DAT: 3"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - John Abowd Tour 201 Caldwell "Ciser", March 14, 2000; V-1512; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Antigone, September 15, 2003 - September 24, 2003; V-1513,; DVC: 2.1"x2.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Ballroom, Climbing Wall, July 11, 00; V-1514; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Antigone, September 15, 2003 - September 24, 2003; V-1515 - V-1516,; DVC: 2.1"x2.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - CCE Promo II, V-1517; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Antigone, September 15, 2003 - September 24, 2003; V-1518 - V-1526; DVC: 2.1"x2.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Antigone, September 15, 2003 - September 24, 2003; V-1527 - V-1542; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Antigone, CD-558 - CD-560; CD's (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Antigone, DVD-528; DVD (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - BCERF - 3 Dramatizations, produced by Park Productions, September 5, 2001; V-1543; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Malcolm Bilson, September 18, 2004; tr8317; DAT: 3"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Malcolm Bilson, produced by DuArt, May 20, 2004; V-1544 - V-1546; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Malcolm Bilson, September 18, 2004 - August 12, 2005; V-1547 - V-1554; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Malcolm Bilson, V-1555; DVC: 3.9"x2.5" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - CCE Promo, tr8318; DAT: 3"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - CCE Director Candidate Steve Hamilton, V-1556; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Class of '52 Reunion, 1997; V-1557 - V-1560; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Collegetown, produced by Gary I., February 23, 2005; V-1561; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Commencement test viewings (GiGi tape), 2002; V-1562; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Cooperative Extension, Long Island - oyster farming, October 15, 1998; V-1563; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Cornell Networking, V-1564 - V-1565; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Cornell Promo: students saying motto, V-1566; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Cornell Seal, V-1567; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Cybertower, August 10, 2001 - January 16, 2002; V-1568 - V-1572; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Cybertower, V-1573 - V-1576; DVC: 3.9"x2.5" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - DA 2, V-1577; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - DB 1, V-1578; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Dig, March 7, 05; V-1579; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Digging Dirt, March 7, 05; V-1580; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Dillard speech, V-1581; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Falling weight deflectometer, Harrisburg, September 24, 2008 - September 25, 2008; V-1582 - V-1584; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - FarmNet: Vitale farm, July 20, 2005; V-1585; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Funini Narration Files, CD-561; CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Nadine Gordimer interview by Michelle Moody-Adams, July 24, 2007; V-1586; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Reading Gordimer Book, V-1587; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Greek Peak (do not use), V-1588; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Ground Breaking narration, produced by CALS, tr8319; DAT: 3"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Ground Breaking footage: Upper Alumni Field, March 7, 2005; V-1589; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Hotel Job Interviews Studio Tapes #1-2, November 23, 2004; V-1590 - V-1591; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Hotel: Sarr Chalmers, Xian Gracia, December 17, 2004; V-1592; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Into the Streets, 11-02-2007; V-1593; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Kafka book discussion with gymnasts, August 23, 2004; V-1594; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Murthy Lecture, October 16, 2003; V-1595; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - NEES promo, October 2004; V-1596 - V-1597; DVC: 3.9"x2.5" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - NYS College Of Human Ecology: Pioneers in a New Century, December 2001; V-1598, c. 1-2; DVC: 3.9"x2.5" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - NYS College Of Human Ecology: Pioneers in a New Century, produced by NYS Coll. Of Human Ecology, December 2001; V-1599 - V-1600; DVC: 3.9"x2.5" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Project #111: #19781, N. Campus Res. Initiative Community Commons/Dr. Ripple/Jazz, February 26, 2002; V-1601; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - FWD - David Orr, January 3, 2008; V-1602; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Painting Class, September 27, 2000; V-1603; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Open House, Lorry tape, V-1604; DVC: 3.9"x2.5" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - PAR Binghamton Teen Assessment Project, May 4, 2001; V-1605; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - PAR Fred Piehl, March 7, 99; V-1606; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - PAR Davydd Greenwood, Scott Peters, May 9, 01 - May 10, 2001; V-1607; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - PAR George & Matt/Interviews at Inlet from Farmers Market, Helen Heward, May 22, 2001; V-1608; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - PAR Interlaken, April 25, 2001; V-1609; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - PAR Jacksonville training, Dick Coogern, Intvw, V-1610 - V-1611; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - PAR Waverly Family Resource Center, V-1612 - V-1613; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Plantations, May 23, 2001, n.d.; V-1614 - V-1623; DVC: 3.9"x2.5" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Pledge, V-1624; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Punta Cana, V-1625 - V-1628; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Ribbon Ceremony, V-1629 - V-1630; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Segs for Expo, January 9, 2003; V-1631; DVC: 3.9"x2.5" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Sierra Nevadas, Shanghai Streets, February 27, 2008; V-1632; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Software ownership, May 12, 1998; V-1633 - V-1634; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Things from America, August 21, 2005; V-1635; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Time Lapse, V-1636; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Trustees video, October 1-3, 2001; V-1637; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Trustees video, October 4, 2001; V-1638; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Message to CCE Boards of Directors by Helene Dellard, 2003; V-1639; DVC: 3.9"x2.5" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Message to CCE Boards of Directors by Helene Dellard, 2003; V-1640; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Wall Climbing, Architecture class Roberts Hall, October 10-11, 2000; V-1641; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - You Tube, V-1642; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Unidentified, March 4, 1999; V-1643; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Unidentified, March 4, 1999; V-1644; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - 4H, V-1645; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Unidentified, V-1646; DVC: 1.9"x2.6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - C, V-1647; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - R, V-1648; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Unidentified, V-1649; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Unidentified, V-1650; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Unidentified, CD-562; CD (Box 35-14-3773 - 1)
    - Maple Production School, 1993; V-1651 - V-1654; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 2)
    - Maple Production School, 1994; V-1655 - V-1661; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 2)
    - Maple Production School, 1995; V-1662 - V-1665; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 2)
    - Maple Production School, 1996; V-1666; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 2)
    - Maple Production School, V-1667; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 2)
    - Maple Production School, 1996; V-1668 - V-1669; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 2)
    - Maple Production School, 1998; V-1670 - V-1671; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 3)
    - Maple Production School, 1999; V-1672; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 3)
    - Cornell vs. R.P.I., ECAC, hockey, March 10, 1990; V-1673 - V-1674; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 3)
    - Cornell vs. Colgate, at C. U., hockey, November 27, 1991; V-1675 - V-1677; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 3)
    - Cornell vs. Colgate, hockey, January 15, 1992; V-1678 - V-1679; Beta 10.4”x6” (Box 35-14-3773 - 3)
    - Cornell vs. Brown, hockey, February 15, 1992; V-1680 - V-1681; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 3)
    - Yale pre-game tape 3, football, November 8, 1986; V-1682; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 3)
    - PBS Promo tape 2, football, September 28, 86; V-1683; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 3)
    - Spring barbecue tape 2, football, 1987; V-1684; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 3)
    - Football time trials, spring picnic, May 1988; V-1685; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 3)
    - Field cam, tape 1, Princeton, football, September 17, 1988; V-1686; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 3)
    - Penn Press Box - 1, football, November 19, 1988; V-1687; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 3)
    - Yale, football, November 4, 1989; V-1688 - V-1691; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 3)
    - Dick Schultz, Holiday Inn, May 30, 1990; V-1692; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 4)
    - Cornell vs. Columbia, tape 1, football, November 10, 1990; V-1693; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 4)
    - Cornell vs. Penn, November 17, 1990; V-1694 - V-1699; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 4)
    - Football Hilites, 1990; V-1700; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 4)
    - Cornell vs. North Carolina, basketball, January 3, 1991; V-1701 - V-1702; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 4)
    - Football team golf outing with Coach Hofhel, tape 3, August 8, 1991; V-1703; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 4)
    - Col. Field, ½"-1" boil, November 12; V-1704; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 4)
    - Home Buyers, Rhonda Meador, Marty Preston, V-1705 - V-1707; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 4)
    - Cindy Noble w- CCESN, October 28, 1993; V-1708; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 4)
    - Program Planning interview, January 27, 1994; V1709; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 4)
    - Waste Management & Parent Resources, V-1710; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 4)
    - Diane Knack, Lead N.Y., August 19, 1993; V-1711; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 4)
    - D. Smith interviews Dean David Call, V-1712; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 4)
    - Lead NY interviews, August 25, 1993; V-1713; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 4)
    - Lead NY interview: Sue Burness, September 1, 1993; V-1714; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 4)
    - Program Planning interviews & meeting, January 12, 1994 - January 19, 1994; V-1715 - V-1716; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 4)
    - 4-H Interviews & "Literature Spread", V-1717; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 4)
    - Science & Tech. in 4-H, Mike Clare interview, February 8, 1994; V-1718; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 4)